Privacy policy | Zaprendo                                     

Toggle navigation [Zaprendo](https://zaprendo.com/)

Privacy policy
==============

* * *

### You and your child’s privacy are very important to us. We never collect personal information from children.

We respect and put you and your child’s privacy above all else.  
This privacy policy was last updated on 4th February 2016.

At Zaprendo, we combine technology with powerful teaching strategies to create educational tools (the ‘Application(s)’ that spark joyful learning. This privacy policy is designed to explain what information we collect through our Applications and our Site (as defined below) and all services provided through the Site and Application (s), (the ‘Services’) and how we may use such information.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the www.zaprendo.com website (the ‘Site’) operated by Zaprendo Holdings Limited (‘us’, ‘we’,  
or ‘our’).

This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors (anyone who browses the Site), subscribers (anyone who downloads the Applications) and users (visitors  
and subscribers who access or use the Services).

If you are unsure about or have any questions on this Privacy Policy and how it may relate to you or your child, please contact us here with any questions.

### What kind of information do we collect?

There are two types of data that may be collected:

1. Personal data or information  
    This is data or information that identifies a user as an individual. Zaprendo does not collect personal data in any of our apps. Zaprendo may collect personal data that parents voluntarily provide on the website such as an email address to receive our updates, blogs and newsletters. See ‘How we may use your personal data below’.We would like to stress that although you may be able to set up accounts on the Application for yourself or your child, we DO NOT collect any personal account information, such as you or your child’s name, chosen Avatar or age through the Application. Such information stays on the Application and is not made available to us.
2. Anonymous data or information  
    This is data or information which does not directly identify an individual or which may have been personal information but has had the personally identifiable information removed. Zaprendo may collect such anonymous data or information about the use of the website and apps.

Examples of such data collected are: amount of time spent on the app, screens visited within the app, information about app crashes. On the Site, we automatically log information about you and your computer or access device. For example, when visiting our Site, we log ‎ your computer operating system type, ‎mobile operating system type, browser type, ‎browser language etc. Please note that information of this type is called ‘aggregate level information ‘. This means that it does not identify the unique user or browser.

We use Google Analytics in our Applications to collect anonymous data, and we do so to improve our Application(s), Site and Services. If you prefer us not to track such anonymous information through Google Analytics, you may opt out anytime, by clicking here.

### How we may use your personal data

We may use your personal information to:

* operate, maintain, and improve our Services
* to respond to comments and questions
* to provide support and customer service
* to send product and service updates, newsletters, blogs, and other information about our products and services
* to protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized,  
    or illegal activity.

### Sharing personal data

We will not share your personal data outside of Zaprendo Holdings Limited or its subsidiaries except in the following limited circumstances:

To comply with laws and to respond to lawful requests and legal processes.

To protect the rights and property of Zaprendo, our agents, customers, and others. This includes enforcing our agreements, policies, and terms of use.

In an emergency. This includes protecting the safety of our employees  
and agents, our customers, or any person.

Those who need it to do work for us, such as such as third party technical service providers involved in the operation of our Site and Services (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed  
by Zaprendo.

We will not use your information for any other purposes.  
How and where we process your data

We respect your privacy. We process your personal information in a proper manner and we shall take generally accepted and appropriate security measures and safeguards to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of Personal Data.

Personal Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following legislative procedures and methods strictly related to the purposes indicated.

Personal Data is processed at our operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact us.

Personal Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the services requested by you, or for any of the purposes listed in this Privacy Policy. You can always request that we suspend or remove the data by contacting us.

Zaprendo cannot and does not guarantee and does not accept liability for any unintentional disclosure.

### Cookies

We may be using ‘Cookies.’ Cookies are small data files stored on your computer or other devices by a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. We do not collect any personal information. This type of information is only collected to make the Site more useful to you; and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs.

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from us at any time.

### Links

We may include links to third parties from our Site or Services. Please be sure to check each third parties privacy policies if you decide to visit them. We are not responsible for these companies and by including them on our Site or Services, we are not providing any type of endorsement.

### Your rights

You have the right, at any time, to know whether your Personal Data has been stored and can consult Zaprendo to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons.

Requests should be sent to us at the contact information set out below by mail or by email contact us.

We use Google Analytics to track anonymous aggregate level information through our Site and Applications. Should you wish to opt out from this, please click here.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to you on this page. It is strongly recommended that you check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the top. If you object to any of the changes to this Policy, you must cease using our Services and can request that we remove your Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data we have about you.

### Contact Us

Zaprendo Limited  
27 Old Gloucester Street  
London  
WC1N 3AX

[\[email protected\]](https://zaprendo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* Sounds English Phonics out now on the App Store and Google Play
* 

© Copyright 2023. All Rights Reserved.
